vombashots.com 2011-12-03

# Welcome to vombanetwork.com

Last updated: February 13th 2007

We recognize that privacy is important, that is why we are committed in to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy statement applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Vomba Network Inc. or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies (collectively, Vomba's "Services")

**Collection and usage of Information**  
The Services we provide, DO NOT require you to register for an account or provide any personal identifiable information to us. In order to provide our full range of Services, we may collect the following types of information:  
  
---  
| **Cookies** – Our Services may store one or more cookies to your computer. We use cookies to improve the quality and ensure security of our Services and personalize online user experience by storing preferences and tracking user trends, such as offering similar Services. Also cookies may be stored to record displayed advertisement on your computer.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but if you have blocked or if you refused cookies from our Services you may not be able to use or install our products and features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.   
  
| **Log information** \- When you use our Services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies

In order to offer you a more consistent and personalized experience in your interactions with our Services, we may combine information obtained through our Services with supplement information we obtained from other companies. For example, we may use services from other companies that enable us to derive a general geographic area based on your IP address in order to customize certain Services to your geographic area.  
  
| **Email** \- We may keep record of email address submitted through our "Send to a friend" feature for fraud and spam prevention only. We do not use the emails addresses collected to send commercial or marketing messages. We do not disclose or sell your email with any other third party.  
| **User communications** \- When you send email or other communication to a site operated by Vomba, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our Services.  
| **Links** \- We may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our Services technology, customized content and advertising.  
| **Other sites** \- This Privacy Policy applies to web sites and Services that are owned and operated by Vomba. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as advertisement or links from within our various Services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. We have no responsibility for the content, policies or actions of these websites.  
  
**Changes to This Privacy Statement**  
We will occasionally update this privacy statement to reflect changes in our Services and customer feedback. When we post changes to this Statement, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this statement. The continued use of our Services following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will mean you accept those changes.

**Contacting Us**  
We welcome your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you have questions about this statement, want to correct, update or delete personal information from our database or believe that we have not adhered to it, please contact us at [privacy@vomba.com](mailto:privacy@vomba.com)
